{
  "classes": [
    "ORG",
    "DATE",
    "MONEY",
    "PERCENT",
    "PRODUCT",
    "SEGMENT",
    "LOCATION",
    "DEPARTMENT",
    "TECHNOLOGY"
  ],
  "annotations": [
    [
      "Apple Inc. reported strong financial performance for the fourth quarter of FY2025, with total revenue reaching $97.4 billion, marking a 6.8% year-over-year increase driven primarily by higher iPhone and Services sales. The company’s net income stood at $24.6 billion, supported by robust demand across North America and Asia-Pacific regions, despite ongoing global supply chain constraints.\r",
      {
        "entities": [
          [
            0,
            10,
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            57,
            81,
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            111,
            124,
            "MONEY"
          ],
          [
            136,
            140,
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            192,
            198,
            "PRODUCT"
          ],
          [
            203,
            218,
            "SEGMENT"
          ],
          [
            253,
            266,
            "MONEY"
          ],
          [
            302,
            315,
            "LOCATION"
          ],
          [
            320,
            332,
            "LOCATION"
          ]
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      "Operating expenses rose modestly by 3.2%, mainly due to increased R&D spending on artificial intelligence and wearable technologies. Apple also announced a $20 billion share repurchase program, reflecting continued confidence in its long-term growth and cash flow stability.",
      {
        "entities": [
          [
            36,
            40,
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            66,
            69,
            "DEPARTMENT"
          ],
          [
            82,
            105,
            "TECHNOLOGY"
          ],
          [
            110,
            132,
            "TECHNOLOGY"
          ],
          [
            133,
            138,
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            156,
            167,
            "MONEY"
          ]
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      "Market analysts at MorganEast Research, based in Singapore, forecast that the Indian digital lending sector will surpass ₹1.8 lakh crore in transaction volume by 2027, with Aurora capturing approximately 6.4% market share.",
      {
        "entities": [
          [
            23,
            43,
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            54,
            63,
            "LOCATION"
          ],
          [
            118,
            135,
            "MONEY"
          ],
          [
            160,
            164,
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            170,
            176,
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            201,
            205,
            "PERCENT"
          ]
        ]
      }
    ]
  ]
}