{"classes":["DATE","ORG","PERSON","MONEY"],"annotations":[null,null,null,["Date: 15 July 2025",{"entities":[]}],["Prepared by: Financial Research Division, HSBC Global Markets",{"entities":[[42,61,"DATE"]]}],["Reviewed by: Priya Sharma, Senior Financial Analyst",{"entities":[[13,25,"PERSON"]]}],["Approved by: Dr. Rohan Kapoor, Chief Economist, HSBC India",{"entities":[[13,29,"PERSON"],[48,58,"ORG"]]}],null,null,["During the second quarter of 2025, global financial markets demonstrated moderate volatility influenced by fluctuations in crude oil prices and central bank interest rate decisions. The Indian market, represented by the NSE and BSE indices, showed an average growth of 3.7% compared to the previous quarter. Notably, Reliance Industries Limited (RIL) and Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) were key contributors to market capitalization growth.",{"entities":[[11,33,"DATE"],[317,344,"ORG"],[355,380,"ORG"]]}],null,null,["1. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) maintained the repo rate at 6.5% in its monetary policy meeting held on 7 June 2025. Governor Shaktikanta Das emphasized a cautious approach toward inflation control.",{"entities":[[3,19,"ORG"],[107,119,"DATE"],[129,144,"PERSON"]]}],["2. Infosys Limited reported a quarterly revenue of USD 4.8 billion for the quarter ending 30 June 2025, representing a 9.2% year-on-year growth.",{"entities":[[0,10,"ORG"],[51,66,"MONEY"],[90,102,"DATE"]]}],["3. Morgan Stanley upgraded the rating of ICICI Bank from ‘Neutral’ to ‘Overweight’ on 20 July 2025, citing consistent loan growth and strong asset quality.",{"entities":[[3,17,"ORG"],[41,51,"ORG"],[86,98,"DATE"]]}],["4. On 18 May 2025, the U.S. Federal Reserve released minutes from its previous meeting, suggesting potential interest rate cuts in late 2025.",{"entities":[[6,17,"DATE"]]}],["5. Adani Ports and SEZ Limited signed a $1.2 billion infrastructure financing agreement with the World Bank on 2 April 2025.",{"entities":[[40,52,"MONEY"],[111,124,"DATE"]]}],null,null,["- On 25 March 2025, Larsen & Toubro Limited (L&T) announced the acquisition of TechNova Solutions Private Limited, a Pune-based IT services company, for an undisclosed amount.",{"entities":[[5,18,"DATE"],[20,43,"ORG"],[79,113,"ORG"]]}],["- HDFC Bank opened 120 new branches across India between April and June 2025.",{"entities":[[2,11,"ORG"],[67,76,"DATE"]]}],["- State Bank of India (SBI) introduced its new digital lending platform “YONO Credit” on 10 June 2025.",{"entities":[[2,21,"ORG"],[89,101,"DATE"]]}],null,null,["In the United States, Apple Inc. and Microsoft Corporation continued to dominate the NASDAQ index, accounting for nearly 18% of its total capitalization. Meanwhile, the European Central Bank (ECB) announced a reduction in bond purchase programs effective from 1 August 2025. The Japanese Yen appreciated by 1.8% against the U.S. Dollar following the Bank of Japan’s (BoJ) revised interest rate outlook.",{"entities":[[22,32,"ORG"],[37,58,"ORG"]]}],null,null,["- On 1 July 2025, Paytm (One97 Communications Limited) entered into a strategic partnership with Mastercard for developing next-generation digital payment solutions.",{"entities":[[5,16,"DATE"]]}],["- Google Cloud and Bharti Airtel Limited announced the expansion of their cloud partnership in India on 3 June 2025.",{"entities":[[104,116,"DATE"]]}],["- On 9 May 2025, Amazon Web Services (AWS) signed a three-year deal with the Government of Karnataka to accelerate public sector digitization initiatives.",{"entities":[[5,16,"DATE"]]}],null,null,null,["Reliance Industries | 20.3 | 7.4%",{"entities":[[0,19,"ORG"]]}],["TCS | 7.1 | 8.1%",{"entities":[[0,3,"ORG"]]}],["Infosys | 4.8 | 9.2%",{"entities":[[0,7,"ORG"]]}],["HDFC Bank | 3.2 | 12.5%",{"entities":[[0,9,"ORG"]]}],["ICICI Bank | 2.9 | 10.8%",{"entities":[[0,10,"ORG"]]}],null,null,["The Indian economy remains resilient amid global uncertainties, with foreign direct investment (FDI) inflows reaching $78.5 billion during FY 2024–25. Upcoming quarters are expected to bring cautious optimism as global interest rate cuts and stable commodity prices support economic recovery. Continued reforms by the Ministry of Finance and initiatives under the “Digital India” program are likely to enhance transparency and investor confidence in the financial sector.",{"entities":[[118,131,"MONEY"]]}],null,["Prepared for: HSBC Global Markets – India Research Desk",{"entities":[[14,33,"ORG"]]}],["Date of Submission: 21 July 2025",{"entities":[[20,32,"DATE"]]}],null,["",{"entities":[]}]]}