{"classes":["TITLE","ORG","PERSON","DATE","MONEY","PERCENT","GPE","ACCOUNT","TICKER","PRODUCT","EVENT","EMAIL","SHARES/STOCKS"],"annotations":[["1.  On March 12, 2024, Auron Technologies Ltd. reported a quarterly revenue of $3.8 billion, marking a 12% year-over-year increase. The company’s net income rose to $420 million, while earnings per share (EPS) reached $1.25. Following the announcement, Auron’s stock price climbed 4.6%, closing at $87.35 per share.\r",{"entities":[[13,41,"TITLE"],[79,91,"MONEY"],[103,106,"PERCENT"],[166,177,"MONEY"],[218,224,"MONEY"],[253,266,"SHARES/STOCKS"],[281,285,"PERCENT"],[298,304,"MONEY"]]}],["2. Nexora Bank PLC announced a merger with FinEdge Capital on June 3, 2024, aiming to expand its European investment division. The combined entity’s market capitalization is estimated at €48.7 billion, with total assets surpassing €320 billion.\r",{"entities":[[0,18,"ORG"],[43,58,"ORG"],[62,74,"DATE"],[97,105,"GPE"],[187,200,"MONEY"],[231,243,"MONEY"]]}],["3. Vertex Motors Inc. released its 2023 Annual Report on February 28, 2024, declaring total revenue of $15.2 billion and gross profit of $5.6 billion. The report also cited a debt-to-equity ratio of 0.42 and a dividend yield of 2.1%. Analysts noted a positive earnings outlook ahead of the company’s upcoming EV product launch event.\r",{"entities":[[3,21,"ORG"],[35,39,"DATE"],[57,74,"DATE"],[103,116,"MONEY"],[137,150,"MONEY"],[228,232,"PERCENT"],[309,319,"PRODUCT"]]}],["4. Quantis Pharmaceuticals’ stock ticker (QPHAR) surged 9% on April 7, 2024, after releasing Phase-III trial results for its new diabetes drug, showing a success rate of 89%. The company’s market cap rose to $9.3 billion, and its P/E ratio adjusted to 24.7.\r",{"entities":[[3,48,"TICKER"],[56,58,"PERCENT"],[62,75,"DATE"],[129,142,"PRODUCT"],[170,173,"PERCENT"],[208,220,"MONEY"],[252,256,"MONEY"]]}],["5. BlueRiver Investments posted Q2 earnings on July 25, 2024, with operating income of ₹820 crore and cash flow from operations totaling ₹1,230 crore. The fund’s return on equity (ROE) stood at 18.4%, outperforming its sector benchmark by 3.2%.\r",{"entities":[[3,24,"ORG"],[47,60,"DATE"],[87,97,"MONEY"],[137,150,"MONEY"],[194,199,"PERCENT"],[239,244,"PERCENT"]]}],["6. Helion Software Corp. declared a stock split (2-for-1) on August 19, 2024, reducing its share price from $230 to $115, while maintaining the same market capitalization of $46 billion.\r",{"entities":[[3,24,"ORG"],[61,76,"DATE"],[108,112,"MONEY"],[117,120,"MONEY"],[175,185,"MONEY"]]}],["7.  On September 10, 2024, Trident Energy Group reported a net loss of $110 million due to declining crude oil prices. However, analysts expect a rebound in Q4 2024, citing improved operational efficiency and a planned acquisition in the renewable energy sector.\r",{"entities":[[4,25,"DATE"],[27,47,"ORG"],[71,83,"MONEY"],[160,164,"DATE"],[238,262,"EVENT"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["🧾 Financial Document 1 – Global Market Insights Report (Fictional)\r",{"entities":[[26,67,"TITLE"]]}],["Date: January 18, 2025\r",{"entities":[[6,22,"DATE"]]}],["1. Stellar Dynamics Corp. announced its FY2024 earnings, revealing a net profit of $1.2 billion, up 14% from the previous year. The company’s revenue reached $8.7 billion, driven by its expanding AI chip division. Its earnings per share (EPS) rose to $2.45, beating Wall Street estimates by $0.18.\r",{"entities":[[3,25,"ORG"],[40,46,"EVENT"],[83,95,"MONEY"],[100,103,"PERCENT"],[158,170,"MONEY"],[196,213,"PRODUCT"],[251,256,"MONEY"],[291,296,"MONEY"]]}],["The stock ticker (STEL) climbed 6.3%, closing at $142.10 on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE).\r",{"entities":[[4,23,"TICKER"],[32,36,"PERCENT"],[49,56,"MONEY"],[64,95,"TICKER"]]}],["2. Meridian Financial Services Ltd. declared a quarterly dividend of ₹4.25 per share on January 10, 2025, maintaining a payout ratio of 42%. The firm’s assets under management (AUM) surpassed ₹2.8 trillion, marking a 9.8% year-over-year increase. Analysts predict the banking segment will continue to outperform due to rising loan demand.\r",{"entities":[[3,35,"ORG"],[69,74,"MONEY"],[88,105,"DATE"],[136,139,"PERCENT"],[152,181,"TICKER"],[192,205,"MONEY"],[217,221,"PERCENT"]]}],["3. Aether Mining Co. reported a decline in copper output by 7% in Q4 2024, citing supply chain disruptions and equipment downtime. Despite reduced production, Aether’s total revenue remained stable at $3.1 billion, supported by higher commodity prices.\r",{"entities":[[3,20,"ORG"],[43,56,"PRODUCT"],[60,62,"PERCENT"],[66,73,"TICKER"],[75,94,"EVENT"],[111,130,"EVENT"],[147,157,"MONEY"],[174,197,"ORG"],[201,213,"MONEY"]]}],["The company’s market capitalization stands at $12.4 billion, with shares trading at $53.70.\r",{"entities":[[46,59,"MONEY"],[84,90,"MONEY"]]}],["4. Orion Telecom Group finalized the acquisition of NovaWave Broadband for $2.3 billion in an all-cash deal. The merger is expected to increase Orion’s subscriber base by 28%, particularly in South Asia. Post-acquisition, Orion projected consolidated revenue of $10.6 billion for FY2025.\r",{"entities":[[3,22,"ORG"],[52,70,"PRODUCT"],[75,87,"MONEY"],[144,162,"PRODUCT"],[171,174,"PERCENT"],[192,203,"GPE"],[222,227,"ORG"],[262,275,"MONEY"],[280,286,"EVENT"]]}],["5. Global equity markets opened mixed on Friday, with the S&P 500 gaining 0.4%, the FTSE 100 slipping 0.2%, and Nikkei 225 rising 0.6%. The U.S. Dollar Index (DXY) traded near 102.8, while Brent crude oil settled at $79.42 per barrel.\r",{"entities":[[3,24,"ORG"],[41,47,"DATE"],[58,73,"EVENT"],[74,78,"PERCENT"],[84,92,"EVENT"],[102,106,"PERCENT"],[112,122,"PRODUCT"],[130,134,"PERCENT"],[140,162,"TICKER"],[176,181,"MONEY"],[216,222,"MONEY"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["🧾 Financial Document 2 – Company Highlights Digest (Fictional)\r",{"entities":[[26,63,"TITLE"]]}],["Date: February 3, 2025\r",{"entities":[[6,22,"DATE"]]}],["1. Xenon Aerospace Ltd. (XENA) reported a record quarterly revenue of $5.9 billion, supported by a surge in commercial aircraft deliveries. The net income grew to $780 million, up from $620 million last year. The EPS stood at $1.95, with shares trading at $109.50.\r",{"entities":[[3,30,"ORG"],[49,66,"EVENT"],[70,82,"MONEY"],[108,139,"PRODUCT"],[163,175,"MONEY"],[185,197,"MONEY"],[213,216,"TICKER"],[226,231,"MONEY"],[256,264,"MONEY"]]}],["The company also announced a share repurchase program worth $500 million, scheduled for completion by Q3 2025.\r",{"entities":[[60,72,"MONEY"],[102,110,"EVENT"]]}],["2. Lumina Insurance Holdings posted Q4 2024 earnings showing premium income of €2.4 billion and claims payouts totaling €1.1 billion. The company’s combined ratio improved to 92.3%, and its return on equity (ROE) reached 11.6%.\r",{"entities":[[3,28,"ORG"],[36,43,"EVENT"],[79,91,"MONEY"],[120,133,"MONEY"],[175,180,"PERCENT"],[207,212,"TICKER"],[221,227,"PERCENT"]]}],["CFO Amelia Voss stated that the group will expand its digital underwriting services in Germany and the Netherlands.\r",{"entities":[[4,15,"PERSON"],[54,83,"PRODUCT"],[87,94,"GPE"],[103,115,"GPE"]]}],["3. Zephyr Retail Corp. disclosed plans to launch an IPO on the NASDAQ by April 2025, aiming to raise $1.2 billion to fund its e-commerce expansion. The company’s valuation is expected to exceed $9 billion, based on projected annual revenue of $4.7 billion.\r",{"entities":[[3,22,"PRODUCT"],[63,69,"EVENT"],[73,83,"DATE"],[101,113,"MONEY"],[126,147,"PRODUCT"],[194,205,"MONEY"],[243,256,"MONEY"]]}],["4. Atlas Energy Partners announced its renewable division generated ₹940 crore in clean energy revenue during FY2024. The company aims to reach carbon neutrality by 2030.\r",{"entities":[[3,24,"ORG"],[39,57,"PRODUCT"],[68,78,"MONEY"],[110,117,"EVENT"],[144,161,"PRODUCT"],[165,169,"DATE"]]}],["CEO Rajesh Menon emphasized ongoing investments in solar grid infrastructure and green hydrogen plants across Gujarat and Rajasthan.\r",{"entities":[[4,16,"PERSON"],[51,76,"PRODUCT"],[81,102,"PRODUCT"],[110,117,"GPE"],[122,131,"GPE"]]}],["**5. The cryptocurrency market remained volatile, with Bitcoin (BTC) trading around $42,180 and Ethereum (ETH) at $2,240. Market analysts noted increased institutional interest but warned of liquidity constraints in Asia-Pacific exchanges.\r",{"entities":[[9,30,"PRODUCT"],[55,68,"TICKER"],[84,91,"MONEY"],[96,110,"TICKER"],[114,121,"MONEY"],[216,228,"GPE"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["",{"entities":[]}],["",{"entities":[]}]]}