{"classes":["DATE","ORG","PERSON","MONEY","PLACE","PERCENTAGE"],"annotations":[["On March 12, 2025, BlueRock Capital Pvt. Ltd., headquartered in Mumbai, announced a ₹48.7 crore investment in Aurora FinTech Solutions, a Bangalore-based digital lending startup founded by Raghav Menon. The investment represents a 12.5% equity stake, making BlueRock one of Aurora’s major institutional backers. The company stated that the funding round was oversubscribed by nearly 40%, signaling strong investor confidence in Aurora’s AI-driven credit assessment platform.\r",{"entities":[[3,17,"DATE"],[19,45,"ORG"],[64,70,"PLACE"],[84,95,"MONEY"],[110,134,"ORG"],[138,153,"PLACE"],[189,202,"PERSON"],[231,236,"PERCENTAGE"],[258,266,"ORG"],[274,282,"ORG"],[383,386,"PERCENTAGE"],[428,436,"ORG"]]}],null,null,["According to Financial Insight Weekly, Aurora’s annual revenue grew from ₹26 crore in FY 2023–24 to ₹41 crore in FY 2024–25, marking a 57% year-over-year increase. The firm attributed this growth to the rapid adoption of its mobile-first micro-loan services across Tier-2 cities such as Indore, Kochi, and Nagpur. Chief Financial Officer Priya Deshmukh commented that the goal for FY 2025–26 is to cross ₹75 crore in revenue while maintaining operational profitability.\r",{"entities":[[39,47,"ORG"],[73,82,"MONEY"],[100,109,"MONEY"],[135,138,"PERCENTAGE"],[287,293,"PLACE"],[295,300,"PLACE"],[306,313,"PLACE"],[338,352,"PERSON"],[404,413,"MONEY"]]}],null,null,["Meanwhile, Zenith Bank Ltd., one of Aurora’s key partners, entered into a five-year collaboration agreement valued at ₹120 crore on May 20, 2025. The partnership aims to expand credit access for small businesses in southern India, particularly in Hyderabad and Chennai. The deal stipulates that Zenith will receive a 3.2% commission on each approved loan, while Aurora retains full control of borrower analytics.\r",{"entities":[[11,27,"ORG"],[36,44,"ORG"],[118,128,"MONEY"],[132,145,"DATE"],[247,256,"PLACE"],[261,269,"PLACE"],[295,301,"ORG"],[317,321,"PERCENTAGE"],[362,368,"ORG"]]}],null,null,["In a related development, SEBI released new compliance guidelines on July 1, 2025, requiring digital lenders to maintain a minimum capital adequacy ratio of 10%. Aurora FinTech confirmed that it currently holds a 12.7% ratio, comfortably above the regulatory minimum. However, Raghav Menon stated in an internal memo that the firm plans to raise an additional ₹15 crore by December 2025 to sustain liquidity amid expansion.\r",{"entities":[[26,30,"ORG"],[69,81,"DATE"],[157,160,"PERCENTAGE"],[162,176,"ORG"],[213,218,"PERCENTAGE"],[277,289,"PERSON"],[360,369,"MONEY"],[373,386,"DATE"]]}],null,null,["Market analysts at MorganEast Research, based in Singapore, forecast that the Indian digital lending sector will surpass ₹1.8 lakh crore in transaction volume by 2027, with Aurora capturing approximately 6.4% market share. Their report highlighted the firm’s disciplined loan recovery rate of 96.8% and strong investor governance. Lead analyst Meera Kapoor concluded that “if Aurora maintains its current trajectory, it could reach a valuation exceeding ₹600 crore within the next 24 months.”",{"entities":[[19,38,"ORG"],[49,58,"PLACE"],[121,136,"MONEY"],[162,166,"DATE"],[204,208,"PERCENTAGE"],[293,298,"PERCENTAGE"],[344,356,"PERSON"],[454,464,"MONEY"]]}]]}