{"classes":["LOC","ORG","PERSON","REVENUE","INCOME","SALES"],"annotations":[["In Q1 2023, Tesla Inc. reported total revenue of $23.3 billion, a 24% increase compared to the same period last year. The company’s automotive segment contributed $19.9 billion, while energy generation and storage accounted for $1.5 billion. Tesla’s net income reached $2.9 billion, driven by higher vehicle deliveries and cost efficiencies in production. The Model Y continued to be the best-selling vehicle in key markets such as the United States and China.\r",{"entities":[[12,22,"ORG"],[49,62,"REVENUE"],[242,249,"ORG"],[269,281,"INCOME"],[436,449,"LOC"],[454,459,"LOC"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["Apple Inc. announced quarterly revenue of $117.2 billion for Q1 2023, down 5% year-over-year. Despite a challenging macroeconomic environment, the company’s services segment grew by 6% to $20.8 billion, with strong performance in Apple Music, iCloud, and App Store sales. iPhone revenue was $65.7 billion, Mac revenue declined to $7.7 billion, and iPad sales totaled $9.4 billion. Apple’s CEO Tim Cook highlighted supply chain improvements and steady growth in emerging markets such as India.\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"ORG"],[42,56,"REVENUE"],[230,235,"ORG"],[272,278,"ORG"],[330,342,"REVENUE"],[381,388,"ORG"],[393,401,"PERSON"],[486,491,"LOC"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["Microsoft Corporation reported revenue of $52.7 billion in Q2 2023, representing a 2% increase from the prior year. The company’s cloud business, Azure, grew by 31%, continuing to drive profitability and market expansion. Office 365 Commercial revenue increased by 11%, while LinkedIn revenue rose by 10%. Microsoft’s net income for the quarter was $16.4 billion. CFO Amy Hood noted continued demand for cloud migration and enterprise digital transformation.\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"ORG"],[42,55,"REVENUE"],[276,284,"ORG"],[306,317,"ORG"],[349,363,"INCOME"],[368,376,"PERSON"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["Amazon.com Inc. posted net sales of $149.2 billion for Q4 2023, a 12% increase year-over-year. North America sales reached $93.4 billion, while AWS (Amazon Web Services) generated $22.1 billion, up 20%. The company’s operating income grew to $12.2 billion, reflecting improved efficiency in fulfillment centers and strong holiday season performance. CEO Andy Jassy emphasized that cost-cutting measures and increased Prime membership renewals supported profitability.\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"ORG"],[36,50,"SALES"],[95,108,"LOC"],[123,136,"SALES"],[180,193,"SALES"],[242,255,"INCOME"],[354,364,"PERSON"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["Alphabet Inc., the parent company of Google, reported revenue of $76.7 billion for Q4 2023, up 9% from the previous year. Advertising revenue accounted for $59 billion, while Google Cloud contributed $8.9 billion, a 26% increase. Net income stood at $20.4 billion. Sundar Pichai, CEO of Alphabet, stated that AI-driven search improvements and YouTube ad growth were key contributors to performance.\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"ORG"],[37,43,"ORG"],[65,78,"REVENUE"],[156,167,"REVENUE"],[175,181,"ORG"],[250,264,"INCOME"],[265,278,"PERSON"],[287,295,"ORG"],[343,350,"ORG"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["Meta Platforms Inc. reported total revenue of $32.2 billion in Q4 2023, an increase of 8% from the prior year. Ad impressions delivered across its family of apps grew by 18%, while average price per ad declined by 6%. Meta’s net income rose to $11.6 billion. CEO Mark Zuckerberg highlighted progress in AI-driven content recommendations and the company’s ongoing cost optimization strategy.\r",{"entities":[[0,4,"ORG"],[46,59,"REVENUE"],[218,224,"ORG"],[244,258,"INCOME"],[263,278,"PERSON"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["Netflix Inc. posted revenue of $8.83 billion for Q4 2023, up 12% year-over-year. The company added 13.1 million new subscribers globally, bringing its total to over 260 million paid memberships. Operating income was $1.5 billion, with a net income of $940 million. Co-CEO Ted Sarandos credited the success to popular original series and strategic price adjustments in select markets.\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ORG"],[31,44,"REVENUE"],[216,228,"INCOME"],[251,264,"INCOME"],[272,284,"PERSON"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["NVIDIA Corporation announced record quarterly revenue of $18.1 billion for Q4 2023, up 205% year-over-year, driven by strong demand for AI and data center products. Gaming revenue reached $2.9 billion, while data center revenue soared to $14.5 billion. Net income was $6.2 billion, compared to $1.4 billion a year ago. CEO Jensen Huang noted that AI adoption is accelerating across industries.\r",{"entities":[[0,6,"ORG"],[57,70,"REVENUE"],[188,200,"REVENUE"],[238,252,"REVENUE"],[268,280,"INCOME"],[323,335,"PERSON"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["In the banking sector, JPMorgan Chase & Co. reported Q4 2023 revenue of $38.6 billion, a 12% increase from last year, and net income of $11.2 billion. Wells Fargo & Co. recorded revenue of $20.5 billion and net income of $5.3 billion, supported by higher interest income. Bank of America reported $23.1 billion in revenue, with consumer banking contributing nearly 40% of total earnings.\r",{"entities":[[23,31,"ORG"],[72,85,"REVENUE"],[136,150,"INCOME"],[151,162,"ORG"],[189,202,"REVENUE"],[221,233,"INCOME"],[272,287,"ORG"],[297,310,"REVENUE"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["Overall, despite global inflationary pressures and rising interest rates, major corporations continued to demonstrate resilience and growth across multiple sectors. Technology, energy, and financial industries led the recovery, with analysts forecasting moderate growth through 2024.\r",{"entities":[]}],["",{"entities":[]}]]}